Guide to the Teacher Preparation and Placement Program, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1972-1997; Accession 1998-A-085
  - Special Students Program
    - RBF Conference, Number 2, March 8-199, 1991 (Box 4)
    - State of CT.-SCSC, TP-Mtg., November, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Temporary Incomplete Forms, 1979 (Box 4)
    - Tutor Information, 1988-1989 (Box 4)
    - Tutoring Course Cancellation Notices, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Teacher Preparation-miscellaneous
    - Accounts for State Visit, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep Correspondence, Spring, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep Correspondence, Fall, Folders 1-2, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep Correspondence, Spring #1, 1987 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep Correspondence, Spring #2, 1987 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep Correspondence, Spring #3, 1987 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep Correspondence, Fall #1, 1987 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep Correspondence, Fall #2, 1987 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep Correspondence, Spring #1, 1988 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep Correspondence, Spring #2, 1988 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep, Fall, 1988 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep, Spring, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep, Fall #1, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep, Fall #2, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep State Site Visit #1, 1981-1988 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep State Site Visit #2, 1981-1988 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep State Site Visit #3, 1981-1988 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep State Site Visit #4, 1981-1988 (Box 5)
    - State of CT. Visit, January 25, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Site Visit #1, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Site Visit #2, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Site Visit #3, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Prep Syllabus, 1988-1989 (Box 6)
    - Teacher Prep Syllabi, 1994-1996 (Box 6)
    - Teacher Prep Syllabi, 1995-1996 (Box 6)
    - Teacher Prep Syllabi, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
    - Teacher Prep Withdrawal, 1988-1989 (Box 6)
    - Teacher Prep Withdrawal #1, 1990-1991 (Box 6)
    - Teacher Prep Withdrawal #2, 1990-1991 (Box 6)
    - Teacher Prep Withdrawals #1, 1992-1995 (Box 7)
    - Teacher Prep Withdrawal #2, 1992-1995 (Box 7)
    - Teacher Prep Withdrawal #3, 1992-1995 (Box 7)
  - Students
  - Teacher Prep Transcripts and Evaluations
- Student records and recommendations, 1984-1999; Accession 2001-A-019
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
  - Ada-Coz (Box 1)
  - Cra-Gwi (Box 2)
  - Hal-Ken (Box 3)
  - Kim-Mos (Box 4)
  - Moy-Qua (Box 5)
  - Ran-Spa (Box 6)
  - Sta-Wig (Box 7)
  - Wil-Zil (Box 8)
  - Recommendations A-Z
- Training records, 1991-1998; Accession 2001-A-025
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2033
  - Professional Development
  - Training costs, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adult learning, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2 - 3)
  - Development academy, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 102
  - Opening, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - National faculty, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Training design, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agendas and design, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Notes, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Modules and materials, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Participants, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 30thEvent
  - Super group (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Communications (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Assignments (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Participants (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Anniversary (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 101
  - Opening, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Participants, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Registration, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Design, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Modules, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Notes, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - PA
  - Loose materials, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Design, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - PIR, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Participants, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Comer principal, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Kids, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Dialogue, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Facilitator, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Supers, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Closing, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Training
  - Training, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 21C national event, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - 102
  - Design, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - National faculty, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Participants, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - PA
  - Loose materials, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Principal's dialogue, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Supers, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Participants, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Facilitators, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Design, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Untitled folder, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - PIR, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Literature for development, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - 101, 1997
  - Agenda, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - SPMT, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Opening, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Team closure, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Design, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Participants, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Training
  - Loose material, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Debrief -PA, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Loose material, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Untitled folder, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - 102
  - National faculty, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Loose material, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Registration forms, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Registration, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Modules, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - 101
  - Loose material, 1996 May (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Forms, 1996 May (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Registrations, 1996 May (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - SPMT "How To", 1996 May (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Change mod, 1996 May (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - National faculty, 1996 May (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - SPMT with Pat, 1996 May (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - PA
  - Agendas, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Principals in residence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Registrations, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Keynotes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Situational leadership, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - 101 training
  - Participants, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - SPMT presentation, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Loose material, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Other correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Loose material, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - 102 training
  - Loose material, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Participants, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Debriefing notes, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - National faculty, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Principal's Academy
  - Agenda, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Participants, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Principals in residence, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Track II, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Notes/letters, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Loose material, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - PD/Training, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Orientation, Spring 1994 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - 102
  - Loose materials, 1994 February (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Memos/notes, 1994 February (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - CPCE evaluation: research, 1994 February (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Participants, 1994 February (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Loose materials, 1994 February (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - 101
  - Participants, 1994 May (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Change game, 1994 May (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Research symposium, 1994 May (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Registration, 1994 May (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Memo, letters, 1994 May (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - PA
  - Loose materials, 1994 July (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Participants, 1994 July (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - PD Training
  - Printed material, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Loose material, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Orientation, Chicago, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Topeka; Leavenworth, 1992 December 17-18 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Comer: Leadership academy for principals (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - PD Training
  - PA, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - 101, May 1993 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Training 102
  - Facilitators, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Loose material, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Comer -names/places, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Orientation
  - Fall 1993 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Loose material (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - CPCE Training
  - Orientation participants, Fall 1993 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Overheads/paper copies, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Guide for training module development, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - New York training, 1992 August (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Facilitator training, 1992 May 3-8 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Comer training (Box 2, Folder 129)
- Computer files, 2001-A-089 (Reel 1)
  Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
- Student and administrative records, circa 1982-1996; Accession 2001-A-089
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2031
  - 1995-1996
  - Amity Regional High School, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Branford High School, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Career High School, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cooperative High School, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - East Haven High School, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Guilford High School, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Hamden High School, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - High School in Community, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hillhouse High School, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - North Haven High School, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Sacred Heart High School, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Wilbur Cross High School, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fall 1994-Spring 1995
  - Career High School (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cooperative High School (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - East Haven High School (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Foren High School (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Hamden High School (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - High School in Community (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Hillhouse High School (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - North Branford High School (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - North Haven High School (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Notre Dame High School (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Sacred Heart High School (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Wilbur Cross (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Fall 1993-Spring 1994
  - Amity Regional High School (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Branford High School (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Career High School (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Cooperative High School (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - East Haven High School (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Guilford High School (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Hamden High School (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - High School in Community (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Hillhouse High School (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - North Haven High School (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Notre Dame High School (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Sound School (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Wilbur Cross High School (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Fall 1992-Spring 1993
  - Branford High School (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Career High School (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Cooperative High School (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - East Haven High School (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Guilford High School (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Hamden High School (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - High School in Community (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Hillhouse High School (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - North Haven High School (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Notre Dame High School (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Sound School (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Wilbur Cross High School (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - 1991-1992
  - Amity Regional High School (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Career High School (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Guilford High School (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Hamden High School (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - High School in Community (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Hillhouse High School (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - North Branford High School (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - North Haven High School (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Sound School (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Wilbur Cross High School (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - 1990-1991
  - Amity Regional High School (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Career High School (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - East Haven High School (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Foren High School (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Guilford High School (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Hamden High School (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Daniel Hand High School (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - High School in Community (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Hillhouse High School (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - North Branford High School (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - North Haven High School (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Wilbur Cross High School (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Spring AYA (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Auditing, Fall 1997 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Spring 1997 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - AYA, Fall 1995 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Spring 1995 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Alumni Auditing, Spring 1996 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Alumni Auditing, Fall 1996 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - AYA, Fall 1994 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Alumni Auditing, Spring 1994 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Alumni Auditing, Spring 1993 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Alumni Auditing, Fall 1992 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - AYA, Spring 1992 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Alumni Auditing, Fall 1991 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Fall 1990-Spring 1990 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Teaching of Africa, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Teamwork (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - CEU Activity Proposal (Box 3, Folder 142 - 143)
  - Geography of China and Japan (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Teaching -USSR CEU (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - CEUs, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - Teaching about China and Japan (Box 3, Folder 249)
  - Child Sexual Abuse in the 1990's (Box 3, Folder 250)
  - General Requirement (Box 4, Folder 253)
  - Evaluation (Box 4, Folder 254)
  - Students (Box 4, Folder 255)
  - Faculty (Box 4, Folder 256)
  - Facilities and Resources (Box 4, Folder 257)
  - Early Childhood Matters (Box 4, Folder 258)
  - Special Students Recommendations (Box 4, Folder 259)
  - Teacher Prep (Box 4)
  - Fall 1991 (Box 4, Folder 280)
  - Spring 1991 (Box 4, Folder 281)
  - Spring 1993 (Box 4, Folder 282)
  - Fall 1993 (Box 4, Folder 283)
  - Fall 1992 (Box 4, Folder 284)
  - Spring 1992 (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - Master Teachers Principals (Box 5, Folder 286)
  - Auditing, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 287)
  - Teacher Prep Statements (Box 5)
  - 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 289)
  - 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 290)
  - 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 291)
  - 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 292)
  - 1986 (Box 5, Folder 293)
  - 1985 (Box 5, Folder 294)
  - 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 295)
  - 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 296)
  - 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 297)
  - CEU Correspondence with State, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 332)
  - CEU Courses (Box 6, Folder 333)
  - CEUs, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 359)
  - Graduate Program, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 441)
  - Arca Grades, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 442)
  - AEA Summer Program (Box 6, Folder 443)
  - AEA Grades, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 444)
  - Teaching of Africa (Box 7, Folder 445)
  - Teaching Global Issues (Box 7, Folder 446)
  - Biodiversity (Box 7, Folder 447)
  - Biodiversity (Box 7, Folder 448)
  - Teaching about the New China (Box 7, Folder 449)
  - Quinnipiac River Watershed Symposium (Box 7, Folder 450)
  - Amistad Affair (Box 7, Folder 451)
  - Practical Approach to directing (Box 7, Folder 452)
  - Japan Curriculum Writers Workshop (Box 7, Folder 453)
  - Nature of Landscape (Box 7, Folder 454)
  - Are we having fun yet (Box 7, Folder 455)
  - Russian Culture in Social Context (Box 7, Folder 456)
  - The Beggars Opera (Box 7, Folder 457)
  - Blake in Context (Box 7, Folder 458)
  - The Bog Walk (Box 7, Folder 459)
  - Exploring the World (Box 7, Folder 460)
  - International Perspectives on Population (Box 7, Folder 461)
  - Practical approach to teaching (Box 7, Folder 462)
  - Yale-Hopkins Summer Seminar (Box 7, Folder 463)
  - Teaching of Africa (Box 7, Folder 464)
  - Teaching Global Issues (Box 7, Folder 465)
  - Teaching about Korea (Box 7, Folder 466)
  - Practical Approach to Teaching (Box 7, Folder 467)
  - Advanced Directing (Box 7, Folder 468)
  - Educational Policy and Equality in Schools (Box 7, Folder 469)
  - Geography: Exploring a world (Box 7, Folder 470)
  - Russia in the world (Box 7, Folder 471)
  - School Business Connections Forum (Box 7, Folder 472)
  - Shakespeare Workshop (Box 7, Folder 473)
  - The UN in The World (Box 7, Folder 474)
  - Understanding Japan (Box 7, Folder 475)
  - Practical approach to Directing (Box 7, Folder 476)
  - Geography Awareness Week Workshop (Box 7, Folder 477)
  - Passport to the World (Box 7, Folder 478)
  - Global Impact of Migration (Box 7, Folder 479)
  - Peoples of Russia and the CIS (Box 7, Folder 480)
  - Understanding Japan after the Bubble (Box 7, Folder 481)
  - Teaching of Africa (Box 7, Folder 482)
  - School of Nursing (Box 7, Folder 483)
  - Origins of British Modernism (Box 7, Folder 484)
  - Practical approach to directing (Box 7, Folder 485)
  - Understanding a Changing Global Economy (Box 7, Folder 486)
  - Teachers Workshop (Box 7, Folder 487)
  - Teachers Symposium (Box 7, Folder 488)
  - Teaching about Russia (Box 7, Folder 489)
  - Religion and Conflict as a Global Phenomenon (Box 7, Folder 490)
  - Practical Approach to Directing (Box 7, Folder 491)
  - Teaching of Africa (Box 7, Folder 492)
  - Teaching about former USSR (Box 7, Folder 493)
  - Religion and Conflict as a Global Phenomenon (Box 8, Folder 494)
  - Practical Approach to Directing (Box 8, Folder 495)
  - Teaching about Former USSR (Box 8, Folder 496)
  - Teaching of Africa (Box 8, Folder 497)
  - Teaching about the USSR (Box 8, Folder 498)
  - Teamwork (Box 8, Folder 499)
  - Teachers Symposium (Box 8, Folder 500)
  - Teaching of Africa (Box 8, Folder 501)
  - CEUs, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 502)
  - Teaching about the USSR (Box 8, Folder 503)
  - Teaching Higher Than Thinking Skills (Box 8, Folder 504)
  - Directing Plays (Box 8, Folder 505)
  - Child Sexual Abuse in the 1990s (Box 8, Folder 506)
  - Teaching about China and Japan (Box 8, Folder 507)
  - School of Nursing (Box 8, Folder 508)
  - Teaching about Russia (Box 8, Folder 509)
  - Understanding a Changing Global Economy (Box 8, Folder 510)
  - Practical approach to directing (Box 8, Folder 511)
  - Origins of British Modernism (Box 8, Folder 512)
  - Teaching of Africa (Box 8, Folder 513)
  - Teachers Workshop (Box 8, Folder 514)
  - CEU, 1988-1993; 10
    General note
    Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
- Student records, 1985-2000; Accession 2002-A-154
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
- Student records, circa 1963-1977; Accession 2003-A-032
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2053
- Student records, 1957-1981; Accession 2004-A-101
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2057
- Student records, circa 1914-1983; Accession 2005-A-006
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
- Records, 1991-2007; Accession 2018-A-070
  Restricted until January 1, 2043
  - Other teacher preparation program, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Early childhood education standards and feedback, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Early childhood certification regulations, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Institutional Summary and Self-Examination Report on the Teacher Preparation Program, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Possible expansion of the Teacher Preparation Program, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Certification correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Teacher Preparation Program committee report, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Early childhood education standards, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Student portfolio instructions, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Early childhood education-evaluation and re-certification, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Associate Director search, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Early childhood state (CT) certification course materials, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Elementary education proposal, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Student enrollment and testimonials, Circa 2001-2014 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Teacher Preparation Program student handbook, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Teacher Preparation Program reports, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Educator Preparation Program-self evaluation report, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Proposed Center for Education, Research and Practice, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Assessment report-correspondence and research, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Budget correspondence and certification requirements, 2007-2009 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Connecticut State Department of Education-Early Childhood Education Accreditation report, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 12)